journelle.com 2017-09-28

# Privacy Policy

### Thank you for visiting journelle.com. We are committed to protecting your privacy.

At journelle.com, we are committed to providing you an excellent and safe online shopping experience, as well as a high level of customer service. In order to accomplish this, we collect, use, and share certain personal information. We value the security of your personal information, and we restrict access to your nonpublic personal information to those employees who need to know that information in order to maintain the high quality of customer and product service that is synonymous with Journelle.  
We continuously strive to better your journelle.com shopping experience, and may modify our privacy policy in the future to reflect any modifications enacted. We invite you to return periodically for the most updated version of our online privacy policy.

### Information Collection

We obtain certain information from you when you shop at journelle.com, including your name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, telephone number, and credit card information. When shopping at journelle.com, we may also collect certain details of your transactions and purchases. If you register for an account online or for our newsletter service, we may also ask for other information, such as your birthday and product preferences. To enhance your shopping experience, we may also collect non-personal information such as site usage history.

We collect certain information to process your purchase transactions and also to improve our services to you. We may use this information to send marketing and promotional materials by mail or e-mail, or to contact you for account purposes. We may also use the information for internal purposes, such as analyzing customer preferences and trends making personalized product recommendations to you and otherwise improving your experience when you shop on our website.

When you visit journelle.com, we and/or third party vendors with whom we do business may send one or more “cookies” to your computer. A "cookie" is a small line of text that is stored with your Web browser, which we use to help provide better service to you. Your browser has options to accept, reject or provide you with notice when a cookie is sent. We may use cookies for many purposes, including (without limitation) to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the Website, and to deliver content (which may include product offers) specific to your interests. For example, we and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site. Through Google Analytics, we may also receive information regarding your demographics and interests. We use this information to improve the products and services we offer to customers, measure the success of various marketing programs, discover what types of customers we are successfully reaching and to find new customers who we believe may be interested in our products and services. 

### Security of Information

Protecting your security is very important to us. In our shopping checkout process, we use Secure Socket Layering (SSL) authentication, an industry-standard encryption technology that guarantees the confidentiality of transactions made at our online site. This serves as a precaution to protect your information from third party interception. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online. However, we continuously strive to protect your information and privacy as much as we can.

Journelle will not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.  Journelle may provide personally identifiable information to employees, consultants, affiliates or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on its behalf. In such circumstances, Journelle requires that these parties agree to protect the confidentiality of such information and to comply in all respects with this Privacy Policy.  Journelle may share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Website.  In addition, Journelle may release personally identifiable information:  (i) to the extent it has a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with any applicable law, enforce any provision of the Terms of Use, protect itself against any liability, defend itself against any claims, protect the rights, property and personal safety of any user or protect the public welfare; or (ii) to respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant.

In the event that Journelle is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, it reserves the right to transfer or assign the information it has collected from users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of Journelle’s bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, Journelle may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

### Opt-Out Procedure

When you register your e-mail address with us, you may receive promotional e-mails and newsletters with information about Journelle's new products, gifts, and special offers. You can choose not to receive these announcements at any time by opting out of delivery. To opt out of delivery, check the bottom of any e-mail for instructions on how to edit your e-mail preferences or to completely unsubscribe from all publications.  Journelle also may use your email address for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major website changes or for customer service purposes).  You cannot opt out of receiving emails for non-marketing or administrative purposes.

### Children Under 13

Federal law requires us to take special steps to safeguard children's privacy, mandating that web sites directed at children under 13 follow certain requirements when collecting information on these children. journelle.com is not directed at children under 13, and does not consciously collect any personal information from children under 13.

### Changes to Policy

Journelle may, at its sole discretion, modify this Privacy Policy at any time.  By accessing our website at any time after such modifications, you are agreeing to such modifications.  This Privacy Policy was last modified as of August 21, 2013.

### Special Note to International Users

The web site is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to users in the United States. If you are accessing the web site from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the web site, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

### California Privacy Rights 

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of the web site who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail with "California Privacy Rights" in the heading to info@journelle.com or write us at: Journelle Privacy Rights 159 West 25th Street 4th Floor New York, NY 10001

### Questions About This Policy

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, or the content or practices of journelle.com, you may contact us by e-mail at info@journelle.com or by telephone: (212) 255-7802.
